Frank Stick Papers and Artwork PC.5089
Frank Stick Papers and Artwork
- Papers, 1910-1966 and undated; 45505; 0.020; Stick, Frank
  - Writings, 1924-1965 and undated; 7945; Stick, Frank
    - Ichthyology, 1950-1965 and undated; 7946; Stick, Frank
      - Mead, Giles, 1954-1956; 30936; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954-1956; 30937; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 4)
      - Rand McNally and Co., 1960-1961; 30938; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 4)
      - Rivas, Luis Rene, 1953-1961; 30939; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 4)
      - Scott, 1956; 30940; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 4)
      - Unidentified Piece on Fish, undated; 30941; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 4)
    - Articles and Other Writings, 1924-1963 and undated; 7948; Stick, Frank
      The Articles and Other Writings subseries, 1924-1963 and undated, contains correspondence, clippings, and drafts of articles, vignettes, affidavits, and other short pieces written by Frank Stick on subjects besides ichthyology. Most materials are undated but appear to date from around the 1950s-early 1960s. Some of the pieces in this subseries are unidentified, and some folders contain only fragments. Many of the writings in this subseries relate to conservation and beach erosion control, particularly in the wake of the Ash Wednesday Storm of 1962, including one unidentified manuscript of a book (or series of articles) on erosion control, written near the end of Stick's life, in which he expresses discomfort with beach renourishment as an erosion control method. This manuscript draft appears to be incomplete and extremely disordered. One unpublished story entitled "The Man in the White Suit" recounts a young Stick's chance encounter with Samuel Clemens (a.k.a. Mark Twain), whom Stick believes convinced the staff of Century magazine to hire him as an illustrator. Also included in this subseries are two folders of material related to cancer prevention, including correspondence, research material, and drafts of a diet plan and an unpublished book by Stick entitled Cancer: A Preventable Disease.
      - Affidavit by Frank Stick Delivered in Price et. al. vs. J.S. Grygeil on the Closing of an Inlet Created by the Ash Wednesday Storm, 1962; 30942; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 4)
      - Articles on Fishing, 1924 and undated; 30943; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 4)
        This folder contains the following articles: "Of Fishermen and Fishes" (draft), "How to Write a Fishing Story" (published, Outdoor America March 1924), "Fishing Resorts Near Chicago" (published), and "This is the Damndest Fish" (draft).
      - Articles on Puerto Rico, undated; 30944; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 4)
      - Cancer: A Preventable Disease [Folder 1 of 2], 1926-1956; 30945; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 4)
      - Cancer: A Preventable Disease [Folder 2 of 2], 1926-1956; 30946; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
      - Draft of an Unidentified Article on Building an Ocean Highway, undated; 30947; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
      - Fragment of Unidentified Manuscript on the Destruction of the Outer Banks, undated; 30948; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
      - Fragment of Unidentified Manuscript on Erosion Control, undated; 30949; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
      - The Man in the White Suit, undated; 30950; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
        This folder contains several drafts of an article entitled "The Man in the White Suit," which describes Stick's early experiences studying with Howard Pyle and trying to begin a career in illustration. In it, Stick recounts a chance meeting with a man in a white suit, who is later revealed to be Samuel Clemens (a.k.a. Mark Twain), which led to Stick's first illustration job for Century magazine.
      - The Ordeal of Curtis Gray: A Man Against a Hurricane, 1962; 30951; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
      - Our Endangered Coastland, 1961-1963; 30952; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
        This folder contains clippings, letters, research material, and drafts of an article entitled "Our Endangered Coastland," which Stick submitted for publication in The State magazine in 1963. Most of the material relates to the Ash Wednesday Storm of 1962, as well as other environmental threats to the coast. The article was eventually published under the title "Dunes Can Cure...And Also Kill" in the 9 November 1963 issue of The State.
      - Our Virgin Islands National Park, undated; 30953; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
      - Saturday Evening Post, 1955; 30954; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
        Materials in this folder comprise letters related to an article by Richard Thruelsen entitled "The Island Nobody Spoiled," which ran in the Saturday Evening Post 3 September 1955. The article discussed St. John and the Virgin Islands. Stick appears to have assisted with the article by providing pictures and editorial input.
      - St. John Article, circa 1950s; 30955; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
      - Unidentified Manuscript on Beach Erosion [Folders 1-2 of 4], undated; 30956; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 5)
      - Unidentified Manuscript on Beach Erosion [Folders 3-4 of 4], undated; 30957; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
  - Professional Papers, 1922-1966 and undated; 7949; 0.010; Stick, Frank
    The Professional Papers subseries, 1922-1966 and undated, contains papers related to Stick's career interests, including his work as an artist and his involvement in real estate speculation on the Outer Banks. Materials include correspondence, legal documents, blueprints, and other business papers. This subseries is arranged into two subseries: Art Career, 1922-1966 and undated, and Real Estate, 1926-1966 and undated.
    - Art Career, 1922-1966 and undated; 7950; Stick, Frank
      This subseries contains correspondence, inventories, and other papers related to Stick's career as an artist. Included in this series are two contemporary publications (The Izaak Walton League Monthly and Outdoor America) featuring illustrations by Frank Stick. Also included are two folders of material related to exhibitions of Stick's artwork held during his lifetime. For more information on Stick's art career, including additional publications containing his illustrations, information on posthumous exhibitions, and inventories and photographs of his works, see PC.5001 David Stick Papers.
      - Art Supplies, undated; 30958; Stick, Frank (Item Box 11)
        Art supplies consist of one green eyeshade, one plastic paint pallet, ten paintbrushes, two dip pens, two pallet knives, one bottle of Grumbacher Artist's Quality Casein Painting Medium, one bottle of Art Maskoid Liquid Frisket, one brick of Amaco modeling clay, and seven tubes of paint.
      - Art Supplies: Paint Palettes, undated; 31972; Stick, Frank (Item Oversize Box 18)
      - Completed Pictures Left at Southern Shores, undated; 30959; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Correspondence on Frank Stick's Paintings, 1958-1963; 30960; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Exhibition at Carolinian Hotel, Nags Head, NC, 1966; 30961; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Exhibition at East Martello Gallery, Key West, Florida, undated; 30962; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Izaak Walton League Monthly, October 1922; 30963; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - List of Frank Stick Paintings and Their Prices, undated; 30964; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Marks, Morris, 1964; 30965; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Outdoor America, April 1924; 30966; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
    - Real Estate, 1926-1966 and undated; 7951; 0.010; Stick, Frank
      The Real Estate subseries, 1926-1966 and undated, contains records related to Stick's career in real estate and land speculation. Materials include correspondence, deeds, abstracts of title, purchase and sale agreements, financial records, blueprints and plans, and other papers. Much of the correspondence is between Stick and his associates in Kitty Hawk Land Co./Kitty Hawk Development Co., including David Stick, N. Elton Aydlett, John B. McMullan, and Cyrus Aydlett. Other correspondence is between Stick and various homeowners regarding specifications for improvements or design elements for their homes. Included in this series is extensive documentation of the early development of the town of Southern Shores and the Virginia Dare Shores community, as well as numerous deeds documenting the chain of early ownership of tracts on the northern Outer Banks and Hatteras Island. Researchers can find many more real estate records related to Kitty Hawk Land Co., Hatteras Holding Corporation, and Southern Shores Realty Co., including additional papers created by Frank Stick, in PC.5001 David Stick Papers.
      - Abstract of Title: Kill Devil Hills, Atlantic Township, Jacocks Beach/Hayman Land, 1930; 30967; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Abstract of Title: Roanoke Sound, Evans Islands, 1929; 30968; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Abstract of Title: Kinnakeet Township, Williams Tract, 1929; 30969; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Abstract of Title: Kinnakeet Township, C.T. Williams Sr. Tract, 1929; 30970; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Abstract of Title: Hatteras Township, Fulcher Lump, 1929; 30971; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Architectural Drawings, circa 1960s; 31973; Stick, Frank (Folder Oversize Box 16)
      - Architectural Drawings, circa 1930s-1950s; 31974; Stick, Frank (Folder Oversize Box 17)
      - Blueprints: Piling Arrangements, undated; 30972; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Certificate of Incorporation, Hatteras Holding Corp. (1929), undated; 30973; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Certificate of Sale, Tax Receipts, etc. - Virginia Dare Shores and Hayman Tract, 1931-1932; 30974; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Contract: Nags Head Beach, Leroy Property, 1935; 30975; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Correspondence, 1929-1956; 30976; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
      - Correspondence, 1957-1966 and undated; 30977; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 6)
        This folder includes an original letter from Pulitzer Prize-winning author Paul Green, 10 January 1960
      - Correspondence on David Stick's Resignation from Kitty Hawk Land Co., 1966; 30978; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Correspondence: Puerto Rico, 1956-1958; 30979; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Correspondence Related to Properties in Southern Shores, 1948-1964 and undated; 30980; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deed: Kitty Hawk?, Atlantic Township, Herman A. Tillett/Harris Property, 1946; 30981; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deed: Kill Devil Hills, Atlantic Township, Susan M. Sutton Property, 1945; 30982; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deed: Kill Devil Hills, Hayman Tract (Hayman, Bell, Hatteras Holding Corp.), 1930; 30983; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deed: Kill Devil Hills, Meekins and Partridge Tract, 1927; 30984; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deed: Virginia Dare Shores, Carolina Development Co., 1927; 30985; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deed: Nags Head, Land North of Jule Day Property/Head Quarters Island, 1930; 30986; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deed: Roanoke Sound, Belle Island, 1930; 30987; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deeds and Other Documents: South Nags Head, 1926-1935; 30988; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deed: Kinnakeet Township (C.T. Williams Jr., Allen R. Hueth), 1927-1929; 30989; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deeds, Various, 1926-1947; 30990; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Deeds of Trust and Notes, 1946-1956; 30991; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Federal Housing Administration (FHA) Development, 1936-1940; 30992; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Hasserot, Francis S., 1948; 30993; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - House Plans, circa 1940s-1950s; 30994; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - House Plans, undated; 38801; 0.010; Stick, Frank (Folder Oversize Folder 3)
      - Indenture: Nags Head, Charles R. Evans Property, 1928; 30995; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Kitty Hawk Land Company Financial Records, 1950-1966; 30996; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Koerner, Lillian, 1954; 30997; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Kritzler, Dr. Henry, 1955; 30998; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Lawrence, Harry C., 1948-1958; 30999; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 7)
      - Lease Between Maud Stick and U.S. Transient Bureau for WPA Camp Site, 1936; 31000; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - McMullan, John, 1955-1956; 31001; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Other Real Estate Papers, 1926-1958; 31002; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
        Includes a certificate from the United States Copyright Office registering Frank Stick's copyright to the chapel at Fort Raleigh National Historic Site, which Stick designed.
      - Photographs of Houses (Primarily Designed by John Crosland Company, Wilmington, NC), 1940s; 31003; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Purchase and Sale Agreement: Kill Devil Hills, Meekins and Partridge Tract, Hayman Tract, 1926; 31004; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Purchase and Sale Agreement: Nags Head, Whalebone Beach/Brinkley Tract, 1935; 31005; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Sales Receipt: Buxton, T.S. Meekins Land, 1930; 31006; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Sears, Gordon, 1954-1956; 31007; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Southern Shores Long Range Planning, 1960-1964; 31008; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Southern Shores Realty Brochures, 1950s; 31009; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Taylor, Roger H., 1948; 31010; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Virginia Dare Shores, 1927-1936; 31011; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Virginia Dare Shores Settlement, 1935; 31012; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Vitols, Mickey and Edite, 1954-1956; 31013; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
      - Winch, Frank, 1927; 31014; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
  - Personal Papers, 1910-1966 and undated; 7952; Stick, Frank
    This subseries contains personal correspondence, vital records, clippings, financial records, family papers, and other papers related to Frank Stick's personal and family life. Included in this series are a manuscript draft of a memoir by Charlotte Stick McMullan (Stick's daughter) and a small collection of receipts and invoices accumulated by Stick's parents, Lydia and David, primarily relating to a burial plot at Oak Ridge Cemetery in Chicago.
    - Brown, Aycock, 1951-1955; 31015; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
    - Cairns, Huntington, 1954-1956; 31016; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
    - Canceled Checks: Bank of Manteo, 1949-1951; 31017; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
    - Canceled Checks: First and Citizen's National Bank, 1953-1962; 31018; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
    - Canceled Checks: Guaranty Bank and Trust Co., 1949-1950; 31019; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 8)
    - Certified Copy of Frank Stick's Birth Transcript, 1954; 31020; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Clippings, 1922-1966 and undated; 31021; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Correspondence Between Frank and David Stick, 1953-1965; 31022; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Correspondence: Frank DeFebio Monument, 1961; 31023; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Correspondence: Museum of the American Indian, 1960; 31024; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Correspondence: New York Zoological Society, 1956; 31025; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Correspondence: Outer Banks Recreation Association, 1965-1966; 31026; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Dohm, Howard, September 1954; 31027; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Family Papers, 1910-1959 and undated; 7953; Stick, Frank
      - Manuscript: Memoir of Charlotte Stick McMullan, undated; 31028; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
      - Last Will and Testament of Maud Stick, 1959; 31029; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
      - Lydia and David Stick Papers, 1910-1930; 31030; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Financial Ledger, 1950-1953; 31031; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Financial Ledger, 1952; 31032; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Financial Ledgers, 1957-1963; 31033; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 9)
    - Hill, Reny, 1954; 31034; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
      Reny and James Hill, family friends of the Sticks, corresponded with Frank Stick briefly in 1954 concerning the possibility of retiring to the Virgin Islands. A letter from Reny Hill, dated 18 May 1954, expresses interest in the idea but concern over the potential for racial inequity and an atmosphere of subjugation to develop between the island's natives and the white retirees that would eventually settle there. Hill goes on to discuss increased racial tensions in St. Thomas, stating "I don't think a native of an idyllic island should be willing to trade his dignity and way of life for the prosperity of acting as servant to white householders." In a reply drafted on 9 June of that year, Stick states that "I believe now that our United States is in the gravest danger it has been in since the signing of the declaration of independence, and I believe in my heart that the danger from within is more serious than from without;" and, in a later draft of the same letter, Stick remarks that "I swing more sharply to the left even than Maud or my children, and I think you may appreciate the difficulties I have encountered here in Dare County, where traditional intolerances are so strongly manifested and where the word democracy has little significance other than its worn out defence [sic] of white supremacy." In addition to racism, the letters in this folder discuss plans for the development of the Lameshur Estate, McCarthyism, Communism, and other political and social issues of the time.
    - Huntington, Archer, September 1954; 31035; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
    - Income Taxes, 1946-1965; 31036; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
    - Meeting Minutes, Dare County Chamber of Commerce, 3 May 1951; 31037; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1936-1966 and undated; 31038; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
    - Sharpe, Bill, 1953-1956; 31039; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
    - The State Magazine, October 1956; 31040; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
    - Stock Certificates, 1926-1928; 31041; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
    - Tax Assessments and Statements, Frank and Maud Stick, 1946-1959; 31042; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
    - White, George, 1954; 31043; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
    - Wills, 1959-1966; 31044; Stick, Frank (Folder Box 10)
- Artwork, circa 1910s-1966; 45506; Stick, Frank
  - Fish Watercolors, UNK; 7956; 33GRF-1; 5000.4.570; PC.5089; Painting; Stick, Frank
    - Witch Flounder, Glyptocephalus cynoglossus, PC.5089.1.001; Stick, Frank (Item Witch Flounder, Glyptocephalus cynoglossus)
    - Atlantic Argentine, Argentina silus, PC.5089.1.002; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Argentine, Argentina silus)
    - Capelin, Mallotus vollosus, PC.5089.1.003; Stick, Frank (Item Capelin, Mallotus vollosus)
    - Deepwater Chimera, Hydrolagus affinis, PC.5089.1.004; Stick, Frank (Item Deepwater Chimera, Hydrolagus affinis)
    - Palometa (young), Trachinotus goodei, PC.5089.1.005; Stick, Frank (Item Palometa (young), Trachinotus goodei)
    - Tilefish, Lopholatilus chamaeleonticeps, PC.5089.1.006; Stick, Frank (Item Tilefish, Lopholatilus chamaeleonticeps)
    - Rainbow Smelt, Osmerus mordax, PC.5089.1.007; Stick, Frank (Item Rainbow Smelt, Osmerus mordax)
    - Long-nose Grenadier, Macrourus sp., PC.5089.1.008; Stick, Frank (Item Long-nose Grenadier, Macrourus sp.)
    - Common Grenadier, Nezumia bairdi, PC.5089.1.009; Stick, Frank (Item Common Grenadier, Nezumia bairdi)
    - Atlantic Tomcod, Microgadus tomcod, PC.5089.1.010; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Tomcod, Microgadus tomcod)
    - Striped Anchovy, Anchoa hepsetus, PC.5089.1.011; Stick, Frank (Item Striped Anchovy, Anchoa hepsetus)
    - Flat Anchovy, Anchoviella perfasciata, PC.5089.1.012; Stick, Frank (Item Flat Anchovy, Anchoviella perfasciata)
    - Key Worm Eel, Ahlia egmontis, PC.5089.1.013; Stick, Frank (Item Key Worm Eel, Ahlia egmontis)
    - Permit, Trachinotus falcatus, PC.5089.1.014; Stick, Frank (Item Permit, Trachinotus falcatus)
    - Round Herring, Etrumeus teres, PC.5089.1.015; Stick, Frank (Item Round Herring, Etrumeus teres)
    - Slender Snipe Eel, Nemichthys scolopaceus, PC.5089.1.016; Stick, Frank (Item Slender Snipe Eel, Nemichthys scolopaceus)
    - Conger Eel, Conger oceanicus, PC.5089.1.017; Stick, Frank (Item Conger Eel, Conger oceanicus)
    - Margintail Conger, Paraconger caudilimbatus, PC.5089.1.018; Stick, Frank (Item Margintail Conger, Paraconger caudilimbatus)
    - Gray's Cutthroat Eel, Synphobranchus kaupi, PC.5089.1.019; Stick, Frank (Item Gray's Cutthroat Eel, Synphobranchus kaupi)
    - Yellow Conger, Hildebrandia flava, PC.5089.1.020; Stick, Frank (Item Yellow Conger, Hildebrandia flava)
    - Gold Spotted Eel, Myrichthys oculatus, PC.5089.1.021; Stick, Frank (Item Gold Spotted Eel, Myrichthys oculatus)
    - Sharptail Eel, Myrichthys acuminatus, PC.5089.1.022; Stick, Frank (Item Sharptail Eel, Myrichthys acuminatus)
    - Banded Drum, Larimus fasciatus, PC.5089.1.023; Stick, Frank (Item Banded Drum, Larimus fasciatus)
    - Slippery Dick, Halichoeres bivittatus, PC.5089.1.024; Stick, Frank (Item Slippery Dick, Halichoeres bivittatus)
    - Redear Sardine, Harengula humeralis, PC.5089.1.025; Stick, Frank (Item Redear Sardine, Harengula humeralis)
    - Fringed Filefish, Monacanthus ciliatus, PC.5089.1.026; Stick, Frank (Item Fringed Filefish, Monacanthus ciliatus)
    - Tomtate, Haemulon aurolineatum, PC.5089.1.027; Stick, Frank (Item Tomtate, Haemulon aurolineatum)
    - Atlantic Halibut, Hippoglossus hippoglossus, PC.5089.1.028; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Halibut, Hippoglossus hippoglossus)
    - Gray Snapper, Lutjanus griseus, PC.5089.1.029; Stick, Frank (Item Gray Snapper, Lutjanus griseus)
    - Redfish or Ocean Perch, Sebastes marinus, PC.5089.1.030; Stick, Frank (Item Redfish or Ocean Perch, Sebastes marinus)
    - Longnose Lancetfish, Alepisaurus ferox, PC.5089.1.031; Stick, Frank (Item Longnose Lancetfish, Alepisaurus ferox)
    - Nassau Grouper, Epinephelus striatus, PC.5089.1.032; Stick, Frank (Item Nassau Grouper, Epinephelus striatus)
    - Southern Stargazer, Astroscopus y-graecum, PC.5089.1.033; Stick, Frank (Item Southern Stargazer, Astroscopus y-graecum)
    - Pigfish, Orthopristis chrysoptera, PC.5089.1.034; Stick, Frank (Item Pigfish, Orthopristis chrysoptera)
    - Squirrelfish, Holocentrus ascensionis, PC.5089.1.035; Stick, Frank (Item Squirrelfish, Holocentrus ascensionis)
    - Atlantic Moonfish, Selene setapinnis, PC.5089.1.036; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Moonfish, Selene setapinnis)
    - Vermillian Snapper, Rhomboplites aurorubens, PC.5089.1.037; Stick, Frank (Item Vermillian Snapper, Rhomboplites aurorubens)
    - Rough Scad, Trachurus lathami, PC.5089.1.038; Stick, Frank (Item Rough Scad, Trachurus lathami)
    - Coney, Epinephelus fulvus, PC.5089.1.039; Stick, Frank (Item Coney, Epinephelus fulvus)
    - Sand Perch, Diplectrum formosum, PC.5089.1.040; Stick, Frank (Item Sand Perch, Diplectrum formosum)
    - Mullet, Mugil sp., PC.5089.1.041; Stick, Frank (Item Mullet, Mugil sp.)
    - Greenland Halibut, Reinhardtius hippoglossoides, PC.5089.1.042; Stick, Frank (Item Greenland Halibut, Reinhardtius hippoglossoides)
    - Tomtate, Haemulon aurolineatum, PC.5089.1.043; Stick, Frank (Item Tomtate, Haemulon aurolineatum)
    - Grass Porgy, Calamus arctifrons, PC.5089.1.044; Stick, Frank (Item Grass Porgy, Calamus arctifrons)
    - Florida Pompano, Trachinotus carolinus, PC.5089.1.045; Stick, Frank (Item Florida Pompano, Trachinotus carolinus)
    - Lane Snapper, Lutjanus synagris, PC.5089.1.046; Stick, Frank (Item Lane Snapper, Lutjanus synagris)
    - Pinfish, Lagodon rhomboides, PC.5089.1.047; Stick, Frank (Item Pinfish, Lagodon rhomboides)
    - Spotted Dogfish, Anarhichas minor, PC.5089.1.048; Stick, Frank (Item Spotted Dogfish, Anarhichas minor)
    - Striped Mullet, Mugil cephalus, PC.5089.1.049; Stick, Frank (Item Striped Mullet, Mugil cephalus)